JESSICA WAZILEWSKI

Developer



SUMMARY

Presently working, from home, in a software company focused on agrobusiness, I work with PL/SQL on Oracle for backend and use Oracle Forms for frontend. We are on studying process and starting to adapt all our frontend with Angular 2. I'm attending a graduation for Developing Analysis on Uninter and also took courses like CS50 from Harvard on basic module and Web module.

My pretention is to work as a Full Stack Web Developer. I also have knowledge on Angular2, CSS, HTML, C#, Javascript and have experience with Agil work.

I'm dedicated, responsible, focused and love to learn, since I decided to start on this profession I've been dedicating my time on learning and hope that I can contribute to your projects!

EDUCATION

Developing Analysis - UNINTER

Economics - Unioeste

2015-2020

CONTACT

(45) 99985-0955 / (45) 99901-0990 jessicatenfen@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jessica-tenfenhttps://github.com/jessicatenfen

AGE:

24

CURRENTLY ADRESS:

Cascavel, PR - Brasil

LANGUAGES

English

Portuguese

Spanish (basic)

French (basic)

EXPERIENCE

Maxicon

2021 - PRESENT

Developer

Garra International

2018-2021

Logistics on Foreign Trade